So for the medical model,
因此对于医学模型
it seems that we'd much rather misdiagnose a healthy person as sick and send them for
我们宁愿把一个健康人误诊为病人
more tests than misdiagnose a
把他们送去做更多的检查
sick person as healthy and send them home without treatment.
也不要漏诊病人为健康人  然后不经治疗就把他们送回家
In this case, a false positive is much worse than a false negative.
在这种情况下 假阴性比假阳性更糟糕
So the rule of this model is,
所以这个模型的规则是
I want to find all the sick people.
我想找到所有的病人
I'm okay if I accidentally bring some more that are sick,
可以容忍不小心误诊一些健康人为病人
but I need to find all the sick people.
但必须尽力检测出所有病人
For the spam email model, let's see.
而对垃圾邮件模型
A false negative means a spam email made its way into your inbox,
假阴性意味着你的收件箱会收到一些垃圾邮件
and all you had to do is delete it.
你要做的就是删除它
So it's a bit of an inconvenience.
所以可能会有点不方便
On the other hand, what's a false positive?
另一方面 假阳性会怎么样？
Your grandma, the poor lady learned to type an email only to tell you she bake cookies,
你的祖母 好不容易学会发电子邮件只为告诉你她烤了饼干
and you delete it. That's terrible.
你确删除了它这太可怕了
So here, we want to punish false positives more than false negatives.
因此在这个例子中 我们希望更多惩罚假阳性而不是假阴性
So this model basically says,
所以这个模型基本上是说
"I don't really care if I find all the spam emails but one thing is for sure,
“我不是很关心是否能过滤掉所有的垃圾邮件 但有一点是肯定的
if I say that an email is spam,
我希望如果把一封邮件被标记为垃圾邮件
it better be a spam."
它最好就是垃圾邮件”
So as we can see, the medical model and the email model are fundamentally different.
所以我们可以看到 医学模型和垃圾邮件模型有着根本的不同
The medical model as we saw is okay with false positives but not with false negatives,
医学模型可以容忍假阳性 但必须减少假阴性
since we're okay misdiagnosing
因为只要能诊断出所有病人
some patients as sick as long as we find all the sick people.
我们可以容忍把一些健康人误诊为病人
The email model on the other hand is okay with
另一方面 电子邮件模型可以容忍
false negatives but not with false positives,
假阴性而不是假阳性
since we don't necessarily need to find all the spam emails but one thing is for sure,
因为我们不一定要完全过滤掉所有的垃圾邮件 但有一点是肯定的
that if we do label something as spam, it better be spam.
如果我们把某个邮件标记为垃圾邮件 它最好就是垃圾邮件
For this, we introduced two metrics, precision and recall.
因此 我们引入两个指标  精度和召回率
They will measure the exact things that we want, namely,
它们将精确测量我们想要的东西 也就是说
the medical model needs to be
医学模型需要一个高召回率的模型
a high recall model and the email model needs to be high precision model.
而电子邮件模型需要一个高精度的模型
We'll talk about them more in detail in the next couple of videos.
我们将在接下来的几个视频中更详细地讨论它们